<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SynBioHub-Documentation</title>
    <link>https://synbiohub.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SynBioHub-Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© SynBioHub 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 11:51:20 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://synbiohub.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. Searching for Information</title>
      <link>https://synbiohub.github.io/userdocumentation/searchingforinfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synbiohub.github.io/userdocumentation/searchingforinfo/</guid>
      <description>There are a variety of ways to search for information in SynBioHub, such as using keywords, sequences, advanced searches and SPARQL queries. They&amp;rsquo;re explained in detail as follows:
1.1 Keyword Search To search amongst various records, follow these steps:
  Navigate to SynBioHub&amp;rsquo;s home page.
  In the search box, enter the keywords for the record you want to search for and click on the search button.
  Subsequently, you shall be directed to a list of records matching the keywords that you&amp;rsquo;ve entered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mailing Lists</title>
      <link>https://synbiohub.github.io/questions-and-issues/mailinglists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synbiohub.github.io/questions-and-issues/mailinglists/</guid>
      <description>If you are a SynBioHub developer with a question about SynBioHub or plugin development, please join the synbiohub-dev mailing list and post your question there.
If you are a SynBioHub user with a question about how to use SynBioHub, please join the synbiohub-users mailing list and post your question there.
If you have a suggestion for a new SynBioHub plugin, please make your suggestion here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2. Viewing and Downloading the Information</title>
      <link>https://synbiohub.github.io/userdocumentation/viewinganddownloadinginformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synbiohub.github.io/userdocumentation/viewinganddownloadinginformation/</guid>
      <description>2.1 Viewing the Information There are various types of records on SynBioHub. They&amp;rsquo;ve been divided into the following sub-categories:
2.1.1 Viewing a Record This section consists of a general description of all record pages i.e, this is what a general record page looks like. Additional sections (if any), are further explained in the further sections, under the respective record types. Once you&amp;rsquo;ve successfully navigated to the record&amp;rsquo;s home page, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to view the parameters in this order:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report an Issue</title>
      <link>https://synbiohub.github.io/questions-and-issues/reportanissue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synbiohub.github.io/questions-and-issues/reportanissue/</guid>
      <description>If you want to report an error please see the respective pages.
Note: For enhancements there are contact details in the &amp;ldquo;questions and contact&amp;rdquo; section.
 This GUI documentation API documentation SynBioHub SynBioHub plugins: Please log your issue in the appropriate issue tracker for the plugin found in the table.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3. Registering and Updating an Account</title>
      <link>https://synbiohub.github.io/userdocumentation/registeringupdatingaccount/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synbiohub.github.io/userdocumentation/registeringupdatingaccount/</guid>
      <description>3.1 Registering an Account Following Steps need to be followed for registering onto SynBioHub:
  Navigate to SynBioHub&amp;rsquo;s home page.
  Click on the Login or Register option on the top right hand side of your Screen.
  Enter the following details to complete your registration process:
     Option Name Description     Full Name Enter the name of the user   Affiliation(Optional) You can enter the name of the university/institute that you&amp;rsquo;re currently affiliated to   Email Address Enter the Email Address, through which you want to get registered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://synbiohub.github.io/questions-and-issues/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synbiohub.github.io/questions-and-issues/faq/</guid>
      <description>This section contains frequently asked questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4. Submitting, Managing and Updating Submissions</title>
      <link>https://synbiohub.github.io/userdocumentation/managingsubmitting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synbiohub.github.io/userdocumentation/managingsubmitting/</guid>
      <description>4.1 Submitting For submitting your designs to SynBioHub, following steps need to be followed:
  Navigate to SynBioHub&amp;rsquo;s home page.
  Click on the Submit option and it&amp;rsquo;ll direct you to the Submit page.
  Now, there are 2 ways you make your submissions i.e, creating a new collection and then submitting your resource or submitting to an existing collection.
4.1.1 Creating a New Collection   Select the create a new collection option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5. Data Sharing Mechanism</title>
      <link>https://synbiohub.github.io/userdocumentation/datasharingmech/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synbiohub.github.io/userdocumentation/datasharingmech/</guid>
      <description>There are a couple of ways to share data in SynBioHub. They&amp;rsquo;re mentioned as follows:
5.1 Using the Share Option   Select the collection/design that you want to share.
  Click the share option. Once you click on the share option, a link shall appear.
  Now, copy that link &amp;amp; you can share the link, thereby sharing the resource.
  5.2 Adding an Owner You can also share your design by giving any number of persons access by adding them as an owner for your design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6. Administration</title>
      <link>https://synbiohub.github.io/userdocumentation/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://synbiohub.github.io/userdocumentation/admin/</guid>
      <description>Note: The administration section will only be available, if you&amp;rsquo;re using a SynBioHub local instance. If you&amp;rsquo;re using a global instance, such as this one, then the administration section won&amp;rsquo;t be available unless you have privileged access to SynBioHub.
To access the admin page, the following steps need to be followed:
  Navigate to the home page of your SynbioHub local instance.
  Click on admin, in order to access the administrative settings of your instance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
